As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take
in the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
La la la la la!
Yeah yeah yeah!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're set to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun!
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled.
La la la la la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared.
As long as I keep that feeling there.
With that, let us keep up the pace.
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits.
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices.
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud.
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous.
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
What?
What the heck is that?
A giant's corpse?
Even for a giant, that thing's huge!
Chopper, they'll hear you! Be quiet!
I see you're just as energetic
as your master, little Shadow.
But now I am your new master
yet fear not for I shall
grant you both voice and body
so you may live on as a zombie
abandon your memories and
abandon your remnants of humanity
so you may serve me as an undying
soldier contract
completed it
works like this Shandora you're
supposed to give up all your
memories all the ties of your
past life that means we should
be able to eat on plates right
if you say that again I'm going
to break the plates in your knees
you're scary please Isidri, stop!
Shandora is way too harsh on Dr. Hogback.
Now, awaken!
Shadow.
Your 500 years of slumber
has come to an end!
The shadow is gone.
He's going to you.
Oh, my God.
Who's there?
Crap! We're screwed!
He found us!
Can you blame me for screaming?
We're all going to die!
Kumasi, don't tell me you were conspiring
with those pirates behind my back!
My soon-to-be bride, but
what are you doing here?
A work of art, a masterpiece, just great!
Me!
Hey, what happened to my pride? Damn it!
Where are the pirates?
They ran away!
My super fast!
They're long gone!
Come back! Sanchi! Food!
Wait.
Who's Sanchi? That's weird.
Okay.
Someone want to explain this to me?
When Luffy's shadow entered
that thing, it started moving.
At least we know how the zombies work now.
It really, it really came back to life.
There's only one
explanation for all of this.
That big guy must have Devil Fruit powers.
The first thing that giant
monster said was meat.
That means it doesn't just have Luffy's
shadow, it has part of his personality, too.
I guess so, huh?
This is all starting to make sense now.
It's just like with that penguin we
ran into that was acting like Sanji.
Because even if it kills
me, I'll never kick a woman!
I see.
So you're saying they put
Sanji's shadow inside that thing?
That seems to be what happened.
And the samurai who hit us
with the back of his sword.
All the weird stuff that's
happening on this island?
It's all his fault, isn't it?
This isn't giving people
a second chance at life.
No one would ask for this!
No one would want it.
He's just playing God,
using humans as puppets.
Dr.
Hogback is an amazing
man and a medical titan.
I think he's incredible.
He's not trying to save anyone.
He lied to all of us.
He's nothing more than another villain.
Chopper.
Now's not the time to get
depressed over something like that.
The only people we need to worry
about are our crew members.
I hate to say it, but it's
up to us to save them now.
Can't just run and hide anymore.
We gotta go to wherever
they're taking Luffy's body.
Right.
I think they said it was
going back to the ship.
They must mean the Sunny.
If the same thing happened to Zoro and
Sanji, then they might be waiting there, too.
That's most of the crew of these.
I still can't believe they got caught.
They're supposed to protect us!
Who's the chopper?
What happened?
No!
Let me go! Stop it!
I can't move!
He's too strong!
Well boys say goodbye.
Because today I'm gonna marry her!
Don't be stupid if I can't
even protect one woman!
Then I have no right to call myself a man.
Take this Viper star.
He's disappearing!
No, not me too.
What's going on here?
Now Nami's disappearing?
Nami!
I'm getting another smell.
It's really strong. Help me!
Wait, where are you?
I can't tell!
The rest is up to you, my loyal zombies.
Capture the intruders and
deliver them to Master Moria.
I still can't tell where he's coming from.
Whoa!
It's an armored zombie!
Crap!
There's a whole bunch of them!
A bunch of zombies are
coming from upstairs, too!
Hey, what else?
Give up your shadows already!
Remember, Jumper, we're the heroes here.
We can't have our shadows
taken away like the others.
Shadows for our master.
Not taking zombies, too!
You guys are cheating.
You can't die and there's too many of you.
You've got to fight me one at a time.
No fair.
We just want your shadow, man.
Don't freak out.
Whoa, hold up. Who's that?
Oh, dude, they just purified the...
Get your filthy rotten
hands off of my bros.
I ain't gonna warn you again. Got it?
These guys know our secret!
Who are they?
Damn, we're too late.
Lost Nami, huh?
It's okay. We'll save her. Right, you two?
What the hell I don't
believe it someone other
than that humming swordsman
knows our weakness.
This sucks we can't die
doesn't really work so
there's our motto if
we're all running around
scared of dying we were
told they used this
staircase to transport
people whose shadows
have been cut that makes sense they took
luffy here we were
headed this way too right
before nami got kidnapped
I'm so worried about
her do you think she'll
be okay Yeah if they
wanted her dead they
wouldn't have captured
her by the way do you
have any idea what that
monstrous roar was we heard earlier we
couldn't see anything
Yeah we were trying to see
where it came from but
then we ran into you
that roar was loopy what did you say Don't
worry we'll tell you
everything we saw I don't
think you're gonna like
what you hear though?
Keep it coming!
He's nowhere near done!
How much food can this special zombie eat?
He'll knock out this entire
island's food supply!
My!
That's quite an impressive appetite!
Kumasi!
Would you care to explain the reason
you are hiding those pirates, huh?
Well, see, it's your cut. Stop talking!
It's not cute at all!
Oh, uh, thanks, Onion Guy.
Still, if you're gonna feed me, get more.
This isn't enough.
Also, this food kinda sucks.
Damn it, special zombie! That's rude!
Don't be so cocky!
Who do you think he must
have made me to move?
That includes you, too!
How could you be so rude to
the ruler of Thriller Bar?
Yeah, the master is pretty much
the king of the island. What?
Sorry about that.
This guy over here was the one
who was being a jerk to you.
Don't sell out your friends like that.
While you're eating, listen up, boys.
Five hundred years ago, you were
a notorious and legendary villain.
And now you have been reborn through my
power and will serve as my underling.
Underling?
What?
No way, I have a queen.
The audacity!
I've never seen such a zombie!
This place is small and stupid!
I'mma go outside for a while!
Or maybe I should go out to see and check
out the world! You? On a boat? You idiot!
That's impossible!
Besides, the special freezer's
made of dense sealed steel!
You'll never get out!
Slam your fist into it all you
want, it's not gonna punch!
Pissed off!
Hey, Wyatt!
What are you doing? This is bad!
Force is escaping!
Somebody do something!
That's weird.
I thought my arm was gonna stretch.
Oh, well.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
It'll be just like before you talk big but
then you'll end up begging for your life
while screaming anything
but the afro anything
but the afro wrong this time is different
I don't stand a chance there
are terrifying zombies at
every turn even when I summon
up the courage to cut them
down they get right back
up but they must have some
sort of weak point right at
this rate even if I found the
zombie with my shadow I
wouldn't be able to do anything
to get it back on top of that
zombie faces are too scary
whoa one of our buddies was
purified how'd that happen it
looks like it looks like he
ate some salted grilled fish?
Idiot, was he a new guy or something?
Did he say salted grilled fish?
You bastard!
You're the guy who shadowy
stole a few days ago.
How did you get back here?
Just answer my question.
Which of your zombies has my shadow in it?
If you don't tell me, I'll
scatter fish all over this island.
Huh? Fish, huh?
Fuss, fuss!
What the hell good is that gonna do?
Hold on.
The only other thing it
could be is the salt, but...
But... salt...
But what the hell good is spreading
a bunch of salt around gonna do?
It's salt!
Zombies are still scary after
all, especially at night.
Thank goodness, that's the grasshopper.
Oh, that scared me.
Even so, it's dangerous for me when the
sun is up then I'd be much easier to spot.
Wait! A song!
When you're scared, you should sing
something to take your mind off things.
Now, if I run really fast so
I can't see their scary faces?
and purify each one, I'll eventually
find the one with my shadow.
What's that creepy song all about?
And who's the one humming it? Huh?
What is this?
What happened?
What the hell is going on here?
The eye to the darkness of the night.
All you hear is the humming.
A swordsman with a terrifying face is
going around killing zombies one by one,
trying to find his shadow.
He's devastated our ranks, purifying
every zombie he's come across.
It's a nightmare.
Mistress Verona, there's been an incident.
Shut up.
Don't wake me when I'm sleeping, Kumasi.
Nyohohohohoho!
At last we meet.
Why is he so strong?
I thought he was supposed to be me!
Even though our swordsmanship is evenly
matched, I can't keep up with this!
Give up.
No matter how many times you try to defeat
me, the outcome will always be the same.
But I think I know
what's slowing you down.
Why don't you let me cut off
that bothersome afro of yours?
What? No! Stop it!
Anything but that!
Don't you dare even touch this afro!
You hear me?
Don't you understand?
If you're my shadow, then you have to know
how truly important this afro is to me!
Because of the fact that my body has stopped
growing, my afro would never grow back!
I would be gone forever!
So, who cares?
And though I am your shadow,
I've forgotten everything about
the days we spent together.
As of now, Moria and
Absalom are my masters.
They give the orders, not you.
A walking skeleton that
treasures his afro.
Do you realize how ridiculous you are?
Pathetic!
Stop it, please! Not the afro! No, don't!
Anything but the afro!
How pathetic you are, my former master.
It seems that I have lost.
I accept defeat.
Yet I beg of you, please, let me live.
I'll leave this island immediately.
Go, get out of my sight.
If you were to die, it would
be a problem for me as well.
I've never seen such a pitiful scene.
I don't care what you say.
During these past five years, I've been
thinking of nothing but this second chance.
And I've trained to become stronger!
Huh?
Oh, good evening, Master Absalom.
Have you gotten everything
in order for the ceremony?
Ah, yes.
Everything's ready whenever you are.
My, my.
What a beautiful bride.
Then start it once.
Put her in her dress and
bring her to the wedding hall.
Of course.
Said this thing's bigger than a giant.
What is it, some kind of monster?
Yeah,
that huge crash you heard and all that
crazy yelling came from the same creature!
In other words, Luffy Zombie
is going on a rampage!
Hey, look!
I can see the sunby!
I see.
So that's the way this works, huh?
You land right here on the island,
take a little stroll through
this gate and up the stairs,
Before you know it, walk
straight into the boss's room,
serving him your shadow
on a silver platter.
Somebody lowered the stairs on the sunny.
I wonder why they'd do that.
I don't know what happened while we were
gone, but they totally wrecked the place!
This is the zombies' work.
Their footprints are everywhere.
Huh?
Then you think they're still here?
Joke's on them we don't have anything
worth taking I don't smell any zombies.
So you think the others are really
here won't know till we look.
Look they're right up here the dining
room all three of them those zombies?
Really had a field day with them
while they were knocked out, huh?
It's hard to look at
Still didn't do it, huh?
So you punks want to be lazy, do you?
All right, then
Step aside.
I'm using my bazooka.
I have a more delicate solution
There's a beautiful lady sword master with
a whole bunch of me With meat and swords?
You guys are helpless!